myuct.ac.za 2019-05-09

# ICTS Privacy Statement | Information and Communication Technology Services

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at ICTS. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.

**_Information Collection_**  
**ICTS** is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below.

**_Cookies_**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Advertisers connected to **ICTS** at times require cookies to tract statistics about products and locations, but at no time are these linked to any personal identification. At this time, ICTS uses cookies only for login convenience.

**_Log Files_**  
**ICTS** uses Google Analytics to analyse trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.

**_Sharing_**  
At this time, ICTS does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.

**_Links_**  
Links to other sites outside of ICTS do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to ICTS. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to ICTS for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to ICTS.

**_Surveys_**  
At any particular time, ICTS will conduct surveys for our visitors. Visitor participation for these surveys is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to take part in the survey. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, etc. This information will be used to analyse the data and understand results.

**_Changes of our Policy_**  
If and when our policy statement changes, visitors with Memberships in our databases will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a visitor decides that our policy does not benefit them, they can use the opt-out option at any time.

If you have any questions, comments, or suggestions about these Legal Notices, please use [email us](mailto:icts-feedback@uct.ac.za?subject=Website%20terms%20query).
